Joe Roback

2611 Victoria Drive, Unit 2 Vancouver, British Columbia, V5N 4L3 cell: 604-839-5303 ijroback@gmail.com

Summary

I am interested in working in a front end web dev role where I can use my skills. I am proficient in the following: ES6, HTML5, CSS3, javascript, API's, Gulp, Php, jQuery, WordPress as a CMS, Git and GitHub, Sass, MAMP/Apache,responsive web design, and working in an Agile environment. I am able to communicate effectively with a team and able to learn on site and develop professional skills and experience.

Education

Red Academy

Professional Web Developer Certification

Simon Fraser University

BA Psychology

Vancouver, British Columbia Graduated September 2018

Burnaby, British Columbia Graduated June 2014

Work Experience

Electronic Arts Canada

Quality Verification Dev Support

Burnaby, British Columbia March 2019 - September 2019

The role consisted of assessing software integrations, writing bugs and reports, and investigate issues. Technologies used: PC64, PS4, XB1, PS4 Neighbourhood, XB1 Manager, Perforce, Dev Track, Confluence, Core Time, Frostbite Drone, Trello, Avalanche, Hansoft, Slack/Skype.

Canadian Mental Health Assocation

Word Press Coordinator

Vancouver, British Columbia
November 2018 - Present

Used knowledge of Word Press CMS to update, maintain and create content for CMHA Staff within their theme.

Everywoman's Health Centre

Web Developer

Vancouver, British Columbia August 2018 - September 2019

Worked with in an agile development team along with a design and UX team. Developed a Wordpress website for a local women's health clinic. Built with PHP, JavaScript, CSS and HTML.

References

Available upon request